别逼我今天去上班
Please don't make me go to work today.
为了逃班我连假死都干得出来
I'll fake my own death.
你这长相不配有抑郁症啊
You don't have the cheekbones for depression.
-怎么了? -巨额工作量 还有总是在焦点之下
- What's the matter? - The workload, the spotlight.
-嗯哼 -家庭第一法案被骂惨了
- Mm-hmm. - Getting hammered on the Families First Bill.
民众恨死那玩意了
People hate that thing.
是啊 那玩意就像个被砸过的婚礼蛋糕一样四分五裂
Yeah, it's falling apart like a punched wedding cake.
总统想让我着手
And the president wants me to start getting
促使媒体把它称作Meyer法案
the media calling it the Meyer Bill,
然而他们决定叫它妈咪Meyer法案
but they've decided to call it the Mommy Meyer Bill.
-我这工作是人做的吗 -嗯哼
- My job is impossible. - Mm-hmm.
拿着这叉子 捅我的颈动脉给我个痛快吧
Take this fork, stab me right here in the carotid.
你是这个世界上最有影响力的"小明"了
You are the most influential Mike person in the world.
总统可是因你才赢了她第一场辩论啊
The president won her first debate thanks to you.
你猜怎么着 还有两场呢
Guess what. There's two more.
而且接下来一场与外交政策有关
And the next one's foreign policy.
考试范围是全世界 不划重点
That's basically a quiz on the entire world.
-我应该怎么准备啊? -听我说
- How do I prep for that? - Listen to me.
你要甩掉包袱 好吗?
You're gonna shake it off, all right?
保持镇定 戴上笑脸
Stiff upper lip. Put on a happy face.
今天会是你人生中最快乐的一天
Gonna have the best day of your life.
感谢鼓励
Thank you for the pep talk.
回见... 哎哟卧槽啊 生日快乐
I'll see you... oh, shit. Happy birthday.
抱歉我没有时间给你买礼物了
I'm sorry I didn't have time to get you anything.
我试试下班后行不行
Gonna try after work.
爱你哦
Love you.
我住在真实的美国中一条普通的街道上
I live on a regular street in real America
这儿有真实的树木和汽车
with real trees and real cars.
-哦等着看 -我们的街道上的确有真实的车子
- Oh, wait for it. - We do have real cars on my street.
我不知道假车是个什么东西
I'm not sure what a fake car would be exactly.
哦 你看!
Oh, bam!
敲我的总统范儿呀
I should be president or something.
如果他一早没喝酒 现在也该一喝解千愁了
If he doesn't drink in the morning, he will now.
哦 上帝 你知道我应该提起什么嘛?
Oh, God, you know what I should have brought up?
O'Brien的女儿在大学里给
That rumor about O'Brien's daughter
一票橄榄球运动员吹喇叭的传闻
blowing all those hockey players in college.
那你就要犯错误喽
That would have been a mistake.
大错特错 明明是长曲棍球运动员
Huge mistake. It was lacrosse players.
女士 您今日晚餐的来宾都已经确认好了
Ma'am, your dinner guests are confirmed for tonight.
-噢 -您的放松之夜已经锁定不变了
- Oh. - Your relaxing evening is locked in.
好嘞 我简直等不及了
Goodie. I cannot wait.
今晚我要和以前的小帮派重聚
I'm getting the old gang back together.
九十年代的时候 安纳波利斯完全就是我们几个姐们儿的地盘
Back in the '90s, us ladies totally owned Annapolis.
-的确是我们的 -帮派?
- We really did. - Gang?
你们都有帮派纹身吗?
Did you all have tattoos?
没 仅仅是我老事务所的一群律师而已
No, it's just a bunch of lawyers from my old firm, you know.
你是怎么加入这个帮派的?
How did you get into this gang?
是不是得杀个人当投名状?
Did you have to kill a guy?
你现在可以总统赦免自己了
You could pardon yourself now.
要知道 作为女性 实际上这事早就搞定了
You know, actually, as women, we  really did get it done.
加上我们的丰乳肥臀
Plus we had tits and ass.
真是迷死个人 要风得风要雨得雨
So we had the whole thing going for us, really.
匹兹堡发生了一起枪击
There's been a shooting in Pittsburgh.
共四人死亡 包括开枪者
Four dead including the gunman.
好吧 这他妈 不太好啊
Well, that's fucking not good.
我们为亡者的家庭祈福
We pray for the families.
对啊 而且还希望他们不要求更多的枪械管制
Yeah, and that they don't demand more gun control.
这里说开枪者是退伍海军
It says here the gunman was an ex-Marine.
本该保家卫国却去伤害民众 真是悲哀
Two sides of the coin. It's very sad.
嘿 Sue 让Mike起草一份声明
Hey, Sue, get Mike to draft a statement.
他有办法 以及祈祷者模板
He's got a thoughts and prayers template.
-马上 女士 -哦
- Right away, ma'am. - Oh.
我们接着来看我吧?
Should we keep watching me?
-嗯? -好 好
- Yeah? - Sure, sure.
美国混凝土联邦会议
当我离开白宫的时候
See, when I left the White House,
我从来没想到我会来为混凝土游说
I never thought I'd be lobbying for concrete.
-挺好的 不是吗? -是
- Great, isn't it? - Mmm.
哦 顺提一下 明天我给我俩安排了
Oh, by the way, I set us up
两个早午餐和一个午餐
with two brunches and a lunch for tomorrow.
哦上帝 我明天已经有两个早餐会了
Oh, God, I already have two breakfast meetings tomorrow.
如果我再继续这样下去的话 我的嘴巴要生痛风了
If I keep going at this rate, I'm gonna have gout of the mouth.
嗯 女士们 你们将成为我们的销售诱饵
Uh, ladies, you are going to be our sale bait.
呃 你说的诱饵指的是...?
Um, by sale bait, you mean...?
像你们这样独立自主 接受过良好教育
Independent, well-educated young women like you
性感热辣的年轻女性 能把议员们引诱到小黑屋里去
who also happen to be very hot to lure congressmen into the room
在某种方面来讲 这就是女权主义
in a way that is deeply feminist.
紧接着我们会介绍我们的客户 他们做成买卖
We then introduce our client, who makes a sale
从某种方面来讲 这就是资本主义
in a way that's deeply capitalist.
我不需要和任何人”做”任何事 对吧?
I'm not expected to do anything with anyone, am I?
这是游说 是个值得尊敬的职业
This is lobbying. This is a respectable profession.
帮我个忙 去那边找Linda
Do me a favor. Go see Linda over there.
她有几件稍紧的衬衫 你可以换一下
She has some slightly tighter blouses that you can choose from.
所以 你俩准备好和混凝土心心相硬了吗?
So, you two ready to go hard for concrete?
是的 嘿 为什么这个混凝土活动的列表上
Yeah. Hey, why are there so many security and military people
有这么多安保和军队的人?
on the list at this concrete event?
我们是在和粘土打仗么?
Are we at war with clay?
Amy 军队经常买什么?
Amy, what does the military buy a lot of?
哦我知道 糖果
Oh, I know this. It's candy.
又卖萌 答案是混凝土
Cute. It's concrete, okay?
所以我们带着军队的人
So we bring the military guys along,
让他们榨出国会的钱
they talk Congress into stumping up money
修建墨西哥边境的混凝土墙 这就是生存之道
for a Mexican border wall made of  concrete. Circle of life.
同时服务好几个客户(群P)
Serving several of our clients' agendas all at once.
-天啊 我就喜欢这个 -是的 我也是
- God, I love this. - Yeah, I know. Me, too.
简直太浪了 不是吗？
It's so slutty, isn't it?
这儿就是个招幌飘扬的毛片现场
This place is like a porn shoot with bunting.
上帝啊 杀了我吧
God, kill me now.
早上好 早上好
Good morning. Good morning.
-记者：早上好！ -好的 让我们开始趴体吧
- Reporters: Morning! - Okay, let's get   this party started.
妈咪Meyer法案是否注定失败?
The Mommy Meyer Bill. Is it doomed?
首先 这不是妈咪Meyer法案
First off, it's not the Mommy Meyer Bill.
这是家庭第一...不 这是Meyer法案
It is the Families First... No, it's the Meyer Bill.
它和我对甜甜圈的爱一样注定持久
- And it's about as doomed as my donut habit.
我们能先讨论下家庭第一法案吗?
Shall we talk about Families First, please?
-对 -我怀疑它会钉在山上的耻辱柱上
- Yeah. - I'm afraid it's getting crucified on the Hill.
-就像耶稣一样 -这是我的重要法案啊
- Just like that Jesus guy. - Well, it's my big bill.
难道你认为我会说 这个
You think I'm just gonna say it
不适合 然后把它拿到淘宝上当二手卖掉吧
doesn't fit and put it up on craigslist or  something?
奥布莱恩议员说 如果家庭第一法案通过了
O'Brien just said, "If Families First is passed,
家庭的整个概念都会终结
the whole concept of family will come to an end."
这肯定是我们的梦想啊
Well, that's the dream, certainly,
但我不确定是否能在这一代实现
but I'm not sure we'll achieve it in this generation.
我不管奥布莱恩是不是讨厌它
I don't care if O'Brien hates it.
这是为了那些喜欢它的人制定的
It's for the people and they love it.
-对对对 但还是不对 –啥?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Except no. - I'm sorry?
我不想说我最接地气了
I hate to be the I'm-in-touch-with- the- normal-guy guy,
但我确实是 普通人只愿意
but I am that guy, and they want to pay
为他们自己的而不是其他人的家庭付出
for their families and not other people's.
这可帮不上...
That's not helpful to...
-什么? 怎么了?
- What? What's going on?
-天了噜啊 - 离总统远一点
Holy shit. - Back away from the president.
女士 这儿有个入侵者 我们需要你呆在这儿
Ma'am, there's an intruder. We need you to remain here.
什么? 我是说 好 我说 这是怎么回事?
What? I mean, okay. I mean, what?
我可没料到这事 这是我没料到
I had not anticipated this. This I had not anticipated.
婴幼儿读物都比你会造句 (苏斯博士 《戴帽子的猫》作者)
Well, that sounds like the world's worst Dr. Seuss book.
灵活的时间对大家都有利
Flexible hours benefit everyone.
这是一个常识...
This is a common sense piece of...
有入侵者  大家保持冷静
Intruder. Everyone stay calm.
呆在原地别动
Stay exactly where you are.
好的  全面封锁吧 没人动 就没人受伤
Okay, lockdown. Nobody move and nobody gets hurt.
我们现在不应该是在去地下密室的电梯中吗?
Shouldn't we be on an elevator to a secret bunker by now?
这里没有电梯 也没密室
There is no elevator or bunker.
为什么这里没有一个通向密室的电梯?
Why isn't there an elevator to a secret bunker?
上帝啊 Bill
Jesus Christ, Bill,
你筛糠得跟一条在坑里使劲拉屎的狗一样
you're shaking like a dog shitting a peach pit.
我真心觉得我应该有一把枪
I actually think I should have a gun.
我并没有在说笑 我是真的需要一把枪
I'm not making a joke. I really would like to have a gun.
好 那我们呢 有没有一个恐慌发生时用的安全室什么的?
Okay, what about us? Is there a panic room or something?
Gary 你走哪儿都是恐慌室
Gary, every room you're in is a panic room.
-我们需要找到一个更安全的房间
- We need to find a safer room.
-我要杀掉Tom James和那个贱人
- I'm gonna kill Tom James and that bitch!
那个入侵者就在那儿!
The intruder! Right there!
我的天 一语成谶! 一语成谶! 一语成谶啊!
Oh, my God, shit got real! Shit got real! Shit got real!
-冷静 你在做什么? -他可是有武器的
- Calm down. What are you doing? - It's a weapon.
你拿钟做什么? 告诉他他来晚了?
What are you going to do with a clock? Tell him he's late?
-已经安全了 女士 - 真的吗?
- That's the all-clear, ma'am. - Really?
呃… -哇哦 好
Well... - Wow, okay.
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, gentlemen.
抱歉 我要出去透透气
Okay, if you'll excuse me, I'm gonna go breathe.
-你听到了那些喊叫声了吗? -我听到了
- Selina: Yeah, did you hear all that shouting? - I did.
他在说什么? 你听到他说什么了吗?
What was he saying? Did you hear what he was saying?
谁介意他说了啥? 那家伙蛇精病脑子有包
Who cares what he said? The guy's nutso-bismol.
他说了什么?
What was he saying?
他说  让我起来
He said, "Let me up.
我想杀掉Tom James和那个贱人
I want to kill Tom James and that bitch."
他来这就是为了杀我
He comes here to kill me
却连我的名字都不知道?
and he doesn't even know my name?
-他可能是说Kent吧 -谢谢
- He may have been talking about Kent. - Thank you.
我得去好好尿一大泡
I've got to take a gigantic whiz.
老天 这个入侵事件把我吓尿了
Man, the siege stuff goes straight to my bladder.
就像是狗吐人言那样的惊吓
It's like if dogs could talk.
好了议员 我要去准备你的市政厅会议了
Okay, Senator, I am going to set up your town hall meeting.
-到时见 -非常好 压力飙升啊
- I'll see you there. - Oh, good. More adrenaline.
上帝啊
God Almighty.
-哇哦 -你现在怎么样?
- Wow. - How are you doing?
我不敢相信有人会来这儿刺杀我
I cannot believe that somebody came here to kill me.
和你
And you.
-对对 -对
- Yeah. Yeah. - Yeah.
你身边还是有很多好人陪着你的
Still, you know, you've got good people around you.
-对 –天!了!噜!啊!
- Yeah. - Holy hell!
-我看到他了! 那个入侵者 -你看到啦?
- I saw him! The guy. - You did?
我直接面对他  然后我就
I was face-to-face with him and I was like,
"后退 哥们  别惹毛我"
"Back off, man. Don't mess with this."
-真的吗? -我的肾上腺素已经飚的不行了
- Really? - I have got so much adrenaline in me.
我感觉我必须做点儿什么
It's like I've got to do something.
-你能给我弄些咖啡吗? -好的
- Can you get me a coffee? - Yeah. Yeah.
-加酒的爱尔兰咖啡 没问题!
- An Irish coffee. - Yeah!
- 您要点什么吗? - 不用了
- Do you want something? - I'm good.
- 好 好 好   - 嗯!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Mmm!
- 他跟我很久了 - 是吗?
- He's been with me a long time. - Has he?
- 嗯 嗯   - 看得出来
- Yeah. Yeah. - I see.
嘿 Kim
Hey, Kim.
距离Tom James市政厅活动一小时
嗨 你在哪儿呢? 能不能确保这些旗子
Hi, where are you? Can we make sure that the flags
和幕布对称呢?
are symmetrical to the backdrop?
看起来有点偏了
It looks a little bit off.
顺便说一句 这件T恤很显你身材
That shirt really compliments your figure, by the way.
就是想小小赞扬一下你
Just a nice little compliment for you.
我喜欢这感觉 太棒了
I'm loving this. This is great.
- 没错 我们干得漂亮啊  嘿 灯光师 - 干嘛?
- Yeah, we're killing this. Hey, lighting. - What?
嗨 进展如何? 能把灯光稍微调暗一点点吗?
Hi, how's it going? Can we bring these down just a little bit?
好吧 似乎这效果有点过头了
Okay, I think that's a little bit too much drama,
或许我们可以再往回调一点点
so maybe we just bring those back up just a little bit.
很好 嗯 记下它
That looks great. Yeah, mark that.
这跟之前的有毛线区别啊 傻×
That's exactly how it was, dumbass.
额 好吧 虽然我们不爆粗口 但还是谢谢了
Okay, well, we don't need that kind of language, but thank you.
一 二 三 四
One, two, three, four.
来点带爆破音的词
Hit me with the plosives.
破  猪 奔 跑
Bring back my pig.
- 听起来很爽 - 嗯 是挺不错
- I'm happy with that. - Yeah, that sounds great.
我不想自夸的
I don't want to pat myself on the back,
但我这想法真不错
but this is a great idea on my part.
想想 离开办公室 参加竞选
You know, getting out of the office, going on the campaign trail.
对 还让你忘掉被骚扰这事
Yeah, help you forget about being molested.
声音略大 抱歉
That's loud. I'm sorry.
嗯 呃...额 不
Yeah, well... Well, no.
只是这里所有人都在仰望我们
It's just that everybody thinks we're awesome here.
我是说 我们就是白宫精英 我们就是神一般的存在
I mean, we're West Wing. We're like gods.
Ryan同志 我的生鱼片拿来了没?
Mr. Ryan, did you get my sashimi?
还没 先生 我马上去拿
No, sir, I will get it right now.
必须把它保持在室温
It needs to be at room temperature,
不然只有满嘴冰味
otherwise it just tastes of cold.
好的
Yes.
生-鱼-片
Sa-shi-mi.
- 你们听到了没? -寿司
- Are you hearing this? - Sushi.
注意听"shus"和"mis"
Listen to the shus and the mis.
打扰一下 你们在笑些什么呢?
Wait a minute. What are we laughing at here?
看来有人很是花了心思啊
Someone sure put a lot of effort into that.
不明白笑点在哪
I don't get it.
噢 鸭子叫 因为我鸭埋跌了(闪避)
Oh, duck 'cause I ducked.
很有创意 很有趣
Very clever. Very funny.
我也笑得很嗨
I'm laughing, too.
嗯
Yeah.
老妈 你一会儿得一个
Mom, some days you get an award
我听都没听过的国家的奖
from a country I've never even heard of,
一会儿有人想杀你
then other days people try to kill you.
几乎天天有人想杀我 宝贝
People probably try to kill me most days, sweetie.
别管它就是了
You just have to shut it out.
嘿 我把你今晚和朋友聚餐的菜单拿来了
Hey, I've got the menu for tonight's dinner with your friends.
我可喜欢试吃菜单了
I do love tasting menus.
能看着这一长串菜名
It's so nice to be able to look at a list of food
然后说"全点了" 感觉真好
and say, "I'll take all of it."
哎 别 我只是想逃避一小会儿
Um, no. I just want to hang back
和姐妹们过个慵懒的晚上 懂不?
and have a loose night with the ladies, okay?
披萨就够了
So let's just get pizza.
那来个创意披萨怎么样?
How about a play on pizza?
- 我们可以分个层什么的... - 不要 不
- We could kind of layer... - No. Uh-uh. No.
或者来个开胃菜
Or we could do an "Antipasta"
我们可以做披萨块
And we could do a deconstructed pizza.
好了 你知道我今晚差点被谋杀了吧
Okay, you know I almost got assassinated  today, right?
- 对 没错 - 所以我
- Yeah, you did. - So I
唯一的要求就是你原原本本按我说的做
just need you to do what I'm telling you
啊哈
Uh-huh.
伙计们 这是Aiden Grant
Guys, I want you to meet Aiden Grant.
赢得了
He's the gentleman that won
之前墨西哥边境围栏合同的先生
the previous Mexican border fence contract.
哇哦 你肯定很幸福 也很富有
Wow, you must be very happy and rich.
- 嗯 是
- Yes, I am.
那他肯定也想再赢一次了
So of course he would like to win the new one,
也就是说他得和议员Martin谈谈
which means he needs to speak to Congressman Martin,
但不是现在扯旗的他
but not his obvious erection.
- 啊 没错 - 那...
- Ah, yes. - So...
啊 想想年轻个20岁吧 是吧?
Ah, to be 20 years younger, right?
- 那时我还穿着尿布呢 - 噢 傻眼了吧
- I would be in diapers. - Oh, snap.
好吧 你看 关键就是在他真的骚扰之前
Okay, you see, the key is to jump in
打断他
before it becomes an actual assault.
- 我想我们错过时机了 - 议员先生
- I think we missed the window. - Congressman.
我能看出来你和我们一样
I can see you are as excited about the advancements
对这次坚挺(混凝土)技术的进步感到激动啊
in concrete technology as we are.
我想介绍Aiden Grant先生给您认识
I would like to introduce you to Mr. Aiden Grant.
看 就像这样
Look, it's like this.
缺乏教育和贫穷之间
There is a link... There is a proven link
存在着切实的联系
between the lack of education and poverty,
贫穷和犯罪之间也是如此
and between poverty and crime.
而家庭第一提案能打破这种关联
Families First will break that link.
他卓绝群伦
He's nailing it,
就像芭芭拉·史翠珊唱高音C一样不费力
like Streisand hitting a high C.
我的天 你在哪出生的 基佬湖吗?(美国人相信男同志都爱芭芭拉)
My God, where were you born, Lake Homo?
今早匹兹堡发生枪击案后
After the shootings in Pittsburgh this morning,
你认为是时候严格控制枪支了吗？
do you think that it's time for some stricter gun control?
应对措施很简单
Reaction is easy.
真正理解却很难
Understanding is hard.
凶手难道不也是一位受害者吗？
Wasn't the shooter also a victim?
我们所讨论的可是一位退役海军
Well, we're talking about an ex-Marine here,
一位效力祖国时 精神受到创伤的人
someone whose mind was maimed in the service of his country.
Ben Tom James刚才说凶手也是受害者
Ben, Tom James has just said the shooter is a victim, too.
-创伤后应激障碍 -哦 天啊
- PTSD. - Oh, my God!
灾星James 我不用想就说出这个名字了
Calamity James. And that's just off the top of my head.
-我该怎么做？ -把他拉下来啊 你特么干站着是假人么
- Well, what do I do? - Just get him off, you fucking mannequin.
Jonah
Jonah.
呃 让他停下来 让他闭嘴
Uh, get him to stop. Get him to stop talking.
我并不是说我不会谴责今天发生的事 我会的
I'm not saying I don't condemn what happened. I do.
-谴责本身就是… -你他妈在干什么？
- Condemnation on its own... - What the fuck are you doing?
这样看起来像是在提醒他整理领带
It looks like you're telling him to straighten his tie.
我的意思是我们需要去理解…
What I'm saying is we need to understand...
你们两个没事吧
Are you guys okay?
你们是要在路边拦车吗？ 什么情况？
Are you trying to hitch a ride? What is that?
-不是 你很棒 你很棒 -不是 怎么回事 哥们？
- No, you're good. You're good. - No, what the fuck, dude?
是啊 是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
如果我们要…
If we're gonna take anything...
要不然我们放退场音乐吧
Maybe we could play some exit music
或者按下按钮把气球放下来
or maybe push the button that drops the balloons.
卧槽 好主意 把气球放下来
Shit, that's a great idea. Drop the balloons.
-准备气球了吗？ -没有 我只是举个例子
- Do we have balloons? - No. That was just an example.
既然没准备气球 你他妈为什么要提气球的事？
Why the fuck did you bring up balloons if we don't have them?
我只是脑洞开了一下
Well, just... I was brainstorming.
女士 记者们已经准备就绪
Ma'am, the press are primed.
好的 我开头打算这样说
Good. So I thought I would open with this.
我打算说 “这是
I thought I would say, "So I'm
我今天第二次成为摄机目标了”
in the firing line for the second time today."
很搞笑 女士
Hilarious, ma'am.
-是啊 我知道 并不是很好笑 -不是 我说话语气就这样
- Yeah, I know, it's not that funny. - No, it's just my voice.
-我总是让人觉得是在挖苦 -哦
- I always end up sounding sarcastic. - Oh.
-Gary Gary -什么情况 怎么了？
- Gary! Gary! - What's going on? What?
别让她走出去
Don't let her go out there.
怎么 出什么问题了吗？
What? What? Is there something wrong?
-怎么了 什么情况？ -我说了别让她走出去
- What? What's wrong? - I said don't let her go out there.
神啊 跟我来
Jesus! Come with me.
Tom James刚才大嘴秃噜到了脚底下了
Tom James just shot his mouth off into his foot.
先让她在上面呆个一分钟
Let her up there for a minute,
然后你就上去接受唇枪舌剑
and then you've got to go up there and take the heat.
总统女士 您能
Madam President, can you
确定刚才您所受到的危险等级是多少吗？
quantify what level of danger you were in?
我总是觉得 好像
I always feel as if I'm
我站在你们面前更危险
in more danger when I'm in front of you guys.
这可是我今天
This is the second time
第二次站在摄机小队面前了
I'm in front of the firing squad today.
我真的很感谢
I'm certainly very grateful for the rapid response
特勤队的快速反应
of the Secret Service.
呃 他们处理了那个闯入者
They... they got rid of the intruder...
很安静地处理
s-silently.
那么 我们继续
So, um, moving on.
这个季度的就业数据真的很鼓舞人心啊 同志们
These job figures for this quarter are very encouraging, folks.
我很满意
I'm quite pleased with that.
很遗憾 我只有这么多时间
Unfortunately that is all the time I have.
Mike 是的 我…
Mike, yeah. I'm good.
我现在要鸭埋跌(闪)了
I'm gonna duck out for now.
-被你抓着小辫子了 -是啊
- You got me. - Yeah, I did.
接手吧 你这个小傻蛋
So you can take over, you bozo.
刚才大家都很愉快啊 是吧
We have a good time here, don't we?
Mike 我刚得到消息 Tom James说
Mike, I'm just hearing that Tom James has said
匹兹堡的凶手
that the shooter in Pittsburgh
和他杀的那些人一样也是受害者
is as much a victim as those he murdered.
你支持这一观点吗？
Do you support that view?
很明显
That is obviously...
非常清楚的是… 我们的观点…
What is clear... That our view...
是我们不支持他的观点
Is we don't support that view.
让我们具体分析一下参议员的话
Let... let's start with putting the senator's words
好吗？
in perspective, okay?
嗯
Um...
呃
uh...
语言并不能杀人
words don't kill people,
枪却不一样
unlike guns,
不仅可以而且也杀了人
which can and did.
这是很不好的事 非常不好
Which is bad. It's so bad.
我可以继续
I could go on.
Reece议员几乎就是个瞎子
Congressman Reece is practically blind,
所以你得近距离大动作地挑逗他
so you're gonna have to flirt close and flirt big.
或者 你知道 做些像盲文似的摸摸的事
Or, you know, do some kind of braille  thing.
我可是有政治学学历的 没问题的
I've got a degree in political science. I'll be fine.
是啊 好事都会干上你的
Yeah, a lot of good that's gonna do you.
Tom James刚才对匹兹堡的凶手表示了同情
Tom James just sympathized with that Pittsburgh shooter
这么一来 他的政治脑袋被打开了花
and in doing so has blown his political brains out.
是啊 他刚向所有有枪的傻X们
Yeah, he just made an enemy of every stupid person
树了个敌 那种人可不少
with a gun, and there are a lot of those.
如果我们什么都不做
If we don't do something about this,
我们的枪支和安保客户就会开始疑惑
our gun and security clients are gonna start to wonder
他们到底为什么要付这么多钱给我们
why it is the hell they pay us so much money,
这可不好  因为我需要他们付我钱
which is bad because I need them to pay me
而不是试图在我睡觉时枪杀我
and not try and shoot me in my sleep.
看看这个混蛋 他已经盯上我了
Look at this asshole. He's already got me in his sights.
- 你好 混蛋 - 好吧 我们可以让他上镜
- Hi, asshole. - Okay, well, we just put him on camera
批评Tom James同情杀人犯
and he can criticize Tom James for sympathizing with murderers.
让我们无需参与任何无益的枪支辩论
Stops us from being involved in any unhealthy gun debate.
干得漂亮 你可能是
Very well done. You might
我给过钱的女人里最聪明的了
be the smartest woman I've ever paid for.
你知道吗? 我来办 已经搞定了
You know what? I'm on this. Already done it.
老天 我真的非常
Oh, man, I'm really
享受你们兄妹之间的这种竞争
enjoying this sibling rivalry between you two.
我在想那你对于我们来说是什么
I'm trying to figure out what that makes you to us.
- 爸爸 - 啊
- Daddy. - Ah.
我一会儿打给你
I've got to call you back.
我在那儿快死了 这超出了我的控制
I was dying out there. It was out of my control.
所以真的有什么情况在你的控制之中吗?
So there are situations within your control?
好吧 Tom James不顾后果我行我素
All right, Tom James is a loose cannon
这看起来像是我在最后一刻选择了他
and it looks like I chose him at the last minute,
当然事实确实如此 但是民众不能知道这一点
which I did, obviously, but people can't know that.
我不是梅林(魔法师) 好吗?
Well, I am not Merlin, okay?
我没有魔法汽车 或者其他法师有的什么东西
I don't have a magic car or whatever he had.
我不能把一个支持疯子的疯子包装得漂亮
I can't tie a ribbon around a crazy guy who supports crazy guys.
如果我们需要 你必须把猫王下垂腐烂的阴囊
You'll tie a ribbon around Elvis's sagging, rotten ball sack
打扮得漂亮 Mike
if we ask you to, Mike.
这就是你的工作
That's your job.
我只是说 不要为了这件事
I'm just saying don't rake me over the coals
吼我 好吗?
for this one, okay?
Tom James在美国各地拉屎
Tom James took a crap all over America.
为什么要我铲屎? 我又不是掏粪工
Why do I got to grab the shovel? I'm not a shit cleaner.
这是你的工作 你就是铲屎官
It's your job. You are the shit shoveler.
你就是干这个的
That's what you do.
- 铲屎官 - 有些屎铲不掉
- Shit shoveler. - Well, some shit doesn't get off.
- 什么? - 我不知道那是什么意思
- What? - I don't know what that means.
还有为什么突然之间大家称我的
And why is everybody calling my Families First Bill
家庭第一提案为Meyer妈咪提案?
the Mommy Meyer Bill all of a sudden?
你告诉我把你的名字和提案联系在一起
You told me to connect your name to the bill.
你现在这是什么语气?
What is the tone that you're using right now?
今天很糟糕 女士 我很抱歉
It's been a shitty day, ma'am, I apologize.
- 啊哈 - 您让我将其称为Meyer提案
- Uh-huh. - You asked me to call it the Meyer Bill.
啊哈
Uh-huh.
媒体最近发现把它称为
The press has recently found it amusing
妈咪Meyer提案很搞笑
to call it the Mommy Meyer Bill.
好吧 杀了妈咪 好吗?
Well, kill the Mommy, okay?
因为它在毒害我的提案
'Cause it's making my bill toxic.
就好像把脑癌这个词
It's like they took the word brain tumor
变成Selina囊肿一样
and changed it to Selina Cyst.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请允许我读一个简短的声明
if I may, I'd like to read a short statement.
事实上 不 我...
Actually, no, I'm...
不 我不准备读这个
No, I'm not going to read this.
我要发自内心地说点什么
I'm gonna speak from the heart.
他要自由发挥了 老天 真他妈太有黑道大佬范儿了
He's going freestyle. God, that is so   fucking gangster.
我爸爸总是告诉我
My dad always used to say to me,
"如果你做了错事
"If you do something wrong,
你必须立刻纠正错误"
you've got to try to make it right immediately."
我说什么都无法帮助
Well, there's nothing I can say that's gonna help
受害者的亲人们
the loved ones of those victims.
但是我可以也将要说我...
But I can say and I will say that I am...
如果我让他们更加悲痛
I am truly, truly sorry
我真的真的很抱歉
if I have added to their grief.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
我不能说感觉很好
Well, I can't say that that felt good,
因为明显感觉糟透了 但同时也感觉很好
because obviously it felt terrible, but it also felt good.
干得漂亮 失陪
It played great. Excuse me.
- 好的 - 先生 太棒了和好神奇生的孩子
- Yeah. - Sir, awesome and amazing had a baby
长大了就成了你
and it grew up to be you.
好像演讲就是您的第二语言 先生
It's like words are your second language, sir.
好吧 感谢反馈
Well, thanks for the feedback.
- 我是Jonah Ryan - 哦 是的
- Jonah Ryan. - Oh, yeah.
这个名字总...呼啦啦出现了
That's a name that keeps... popping up.
我是个很受呼-安 欢迎人
Well, I'm a pop-ular guy.
Richard T. Splett
Richard T. Splett.
不知道我什么说了T 我的中间名是John
Don't know why I said T. My middle name is John.
但我是Ryan先生的行政助理
But I'm Mr. Ryan's executive assistant.
所以你是这家伙的副总统?
So you're this guy's veep?
- 算是 算是 - 是的
- Kind of. Kind of, yeah. - Yeah.
很高兴认识你们
Well, nice to meet you guys.
我们应该请您替我们所有搞砸的事致歉
Hey, we should have you apologize for all our screwups.
飓风袭击 Leon West"监禁"
Hurricane washout. Leon West "Detention."
数据泄露
The data breach.
哦 是的 HIV女孩那件事
Oh, yeah, that thing with the HIV girl.
- 不... 是的 - 是的
- No, the... yes. - Yes.
哇哦 HIV女孩
Wow, that HIV girl.
等下...
Wait a sec...
如果我不知道的话 我会怀疑
If I didn't know better, I would suspect
还发生了另外一起数据外泄事件
that there was another data breach.
有吗？
Really?
我觉得 没有
I mean, there isn't.
没有 因为如果有我会知道的
No, because I would know about it.
嗯
Mm.
伙计们 要搭车回华盛顿吗?
Listen, you guys, you want a ride back to DC?
我可以听你们讲讲第一线的故事
It'd be so great to hear some stories
那一定很来劲
from the front line, you know.
我很乐意 但 我有什么会议安排吗?
I'd love to, but do I have any meetings?
没 没有
No. No.
你确定没有任何安排?
Are you sure there aren't any?
啊 哦 有一个会议
Oh, uh, there's one.
好 那就取消它
Okay, good. Cancel it.
但愿它不重要
Hope it wasn't important.
是 不重要
Uh, it wasn't.
所以 现在的情况是 Tom James刚刚道歉了
So here's a thing. Tom James just apologized.
结果怎么样?
How did that go down?
出人意料的很不错 就像伏特加里加麦片
Surprisingly well. Like vodka and cereal.
- 好吧 那 怎么样? 我们放弃枪手吗?
- All right, so, what? Do we lose the gun guy?
- 不 不 保留枪手
- No, no. Keep the gun guy.
枪手们都不喜欢别人拿走他们的东西
Gun guys don't like it when you take things away from them.
但我注意到
But it has made me realize
Tom James提到了心理健康问题
that Tom James talked up mental health issues.
- 我们要找个人跟进这个事情 - 对的
- Let's get someone to jump on those. - Exactly.
我们现在有关于心理健康的慈善项目在计划中吗？
Do we have any mental health charities on the books?
有是有 但那些项目收益不太好
We do, but they don't pay very well.
不管怎么说 这是Germmill制药的Alex Barry
However, this is Alex Barry from Gemmill Pharmaceuticals.
- Amy Brookheimer - 你好
- Amy Brookheimer. - Hi.
- 你好吗? - 像你这样的医药行业大人物
- How are you? - So what is a big pharma guy like you
到这样一个关于混凝土的活动来做什么呢？
doing at a concrete event like this?
是这样的 建筑施工带来工人
Well, construction brings builders.
工人带来性工作者
Builders bring sex workers.
性工作者带来性传播疾病
And sex workers bring STDs.
- 一个良性循环 - 是...
- A virtuous circle. - Well...
嗨 夫人 别起诉我 不过你的律师朋友们在这儿
Hey, ma'am, don't sue me, but your lawyer friends are here.
哦 上帝!
Oh, my God!
你好啊 女总统
Hello, Madam President.
哦 你比以前更性感了
Oh, you are hotter than ever.
- 哦 别这么说 - 我知道!
- Oh, puh-lease. - I know!
你是用了什么 是犀牛角还是猴腺?
What do you use, like rhino horns or monkey
- 你说的我都用了
- All of the above.
- 另外我还做了整张脸 - 哇哦
- Plus I had my whole face done. - Oh.
不 我并没有做过手术 Deborah 绝对没做过
No, I didn't really have any surgery, Deborah. I didn't.
确实没做过... 没有
I haven't had... no.
好了 这是黑刺李杜松子酒
Okay, this is sloe gin
是英国大使送的礼物
and it's a gift from the British ambassador.
哇 好昂贵哦
Oh, how fancy.
这可是酒 你个老酒鬼
It's booze, you old boozehound.
事实上 我保持戒酒纪录
Actually, I have been sober
已经有五年四个月了...
for five years and four months, so...
哦 那...
Oh, well...
我已经戒酒了有27个小时了
I have been sober for 27 hours,
既然如此 那就让我拿走你手里的东西吧
so let me take that off your hand
我要大破酒戒啦
while I jump off the wagon.
我给您来点儿干姜石榴汁雪碧或者干姜石榴汁可乐?
Can I get you like a Shirley Temple or a Roy Rogers?
就可乐 雪碧之类的就好
Just Coke, Sprite, something like that.
- 好的 好 - 苏打水
- Okay, yeah. - Soda.
Benjamin 你想见我?
Benjamin, you wanted to see me?
我是要在这儿被废了吗?
Is this where I get whacked?
哦 不 先生 我们这是要一起吹吹你
Oh, no, sir. This is where we all blow you
因为你他妈的实在太棒了
because you were so freaking great.
- 算了吧
- Come on.
我只是... 我就是...
All I did... I just went...
让人怎么不爱他啊?
How can anybody not love him?
他就像你的父亲 却又很亲和
He's like your dad except he's nice.
这两个家伙他妈的在这里干什么?
What the fuck are these guys doing here?
每一个选手都需要融入到团队里 Ben
Every player needs to roll with a crew, Ben.
这是路人皆知的事实
That's the truth from the street.
这正式成为我最糟糕的一天
This is officially my worst day.
那 好吧 欢迎参加周五晚上的喝酒派对
Well, in that case, welcome to Friday night
你们每周五都喝吗?
Do you guys have drinks every Friday?
只是在最近五年
Only for the last five years.
谁也没想过要叫上你 没什么好说的原因
No one ever thought to tell you for unaccountable reasons.
不管怎样 现在你来了
Anyway, you're here now.
我喜欢波旁威士忌就像我喜欢的女人
I like my bourbon like I like my women...
- 18岁的还湿嫩嫩的
- 18 years old and wet.
- 我就像俄罗斯的白汉子一样能喝 - 给 拿着吧
- I'm more of a white Russian man myself. - Here, take that.
- 好吧 我也觉得这样比较好 - 请坐
- Okay, I guess that's fine also. - Have a seat.
- 别坐那里 - 是 我没打算坐那儿
- Not there. - No. Wasn't going to.
来 我们要为什么而干杯呢?
Okay, so what are we drinking to?
- 敬更多的破事儿 - 更多的破事儿
- To more shit. - More shit.
我们上一次这样聚是什么时候的事了？
When is the last time when all of us were together?
- 安娜的婚礼 - 那是20年前了
- Anna's wedding. - That was 20 years ago.
- 哦 不 是五年前 - 什么?
- Oh, no, it was five years ago. - What?
- 我再婚了 - 她是再婚了
- I remarried. - She got married again.
哦 好吧
Oh. Okay.
其实 也没让我太惊讶
Well, that doesn't surprise me.
是的 他最后终于出柜了?
Yeah. Did he finally come out?
他死了
He died.
- 噢...
- Oh.
我...太抱歉了
I am... so sorry.
没啥的 我的意思是 他不是搞基的
I'm not. I mean, he wasn't gay.
- 他只是个王八蛋罢了 - 嗯哼
- He was just an asshole. - Uh-huh.
我现在还能当着你爆粗口吗?
Can I swear in front of you now?
不 你他娘的不能
No, you fucking can't.
好啦 晚饭时间 一起吃吧
Okay, dinner. Let's do it.
白宫的晚饭呦
Dinner at the White House.
- 吃些什么呢? - 等下你就知道了
- What are we having? - Wait until you see.
好漂亮的房间
Beautiful room.
是匹萨哒!
It's pizza!
就像我们以前一样 小伙伴们
Just like the old days, guys.
- 哇喔 - 那时候我们别的也买不起
- Oh, wow. - When we couldn't afford anything
是啊
Yeah.
额滴神啊 大宴会都吃烦了
Oh, God, so tired of these big banquets.
- 你懂得 六道主菜 真是够了 - 是啊
- You know, six courses. Enough. - Yeah.
甜点呢 一桶冰淇淋配四个勺子吗?
What's for dessert, a tub of ice cream and four spoons?
- 没错 - 噢
- Yes. - Oh.
还有其它什么我们需要知道你发神经的事情吗?
Any other psychotic things that we need to know about you?
我觉得我们应该给所有新泽西的人灭灭菌
I think we should sterilize everyone in New Jersey.
- 好想法 - 我支持给那些在影院侃大山的人...
- Good idea. - I'm in favor of assisted dying
使用安乐死
for anyone who talks in a movie theater.
真是高瞻远瞩
That's forward thinking.
还有 我认为毒品应该合法化
And I think we should legalize drugs.
- 噢 耶!
- Oh, yeah!
我要敲锣庆祝去了
I'll get the bong.
不不不 最后一个我不是说笑的
No, no, no, that last one, that's actually not a joke.
爆个梗 再甩个包袱
Set it up, knock it down.
唯你独尊
Tom James.
我说正经的
I'm serious.
我认为毒品应该合法化
I believe we should legalize drugs.
看到我儿子戒毒这么挣扎
Having seen what my son has been through,
我认为这是唯一的出路
I think it's the only way.
快干死我吧
Fuck my face.
- 好吧 呃... - 如果这话传出去 我就生不如死了
- Okay, uh... - If this gets out, my life's hell.
伙计们 伙计们! 冷静
Guys, guys! Come on.
都冷静下
Everybody calm down.
好啊 那我们抽点大麻 然后磕点安眠药吧
Yeah, let's just smoke a doobie and pop some ludes.
那Deborah 跟我们说说你的近况吧
So, Deborah, give us some updates on your life.
我做了很多无偿的工作
I do a lot of pro bono work now.
-噢 不错呀 -恩 你懂的 家庭调解
- Oh, good for you. - Yeah, you know, family disputes,
在学校开除学生什么的
school exclusions, that sort of thing.
瞧瞧我们 都在做用不同方式做着相同的努力
Look at us, we're working it from both ends.
怎么讲?
How so?
呃 那个 因为我将要通过那项法案
Um, well, because I'm about to pass this legislation.
- 家庭第一提案? - 家庭第一提案 是的
- Families First? - Families First, yeah.
我很为它自豪
I'm very proud of it.
你们觉得怎么样?
What do you guys think of it?
最后肯定会有些事与愿违 显然的
Well, it's not everything you want it to be, obviously,
他们总会加上很多修正法案
becuse they put all those amendments on it.
我觉得这次情况还不错 是的
I think it's in pretty good shape. Yeah.
我的意思是 我认为这将
I mean, I think it's gonna
给人们的生活带来很大改变
make a big difference in people's lives.
呃 也许你没有合理地考虑到那些在税收边缘的人
Uh, perhaps you haven't thought through the tax margins properly.
我们有最棒的金融精英在处理那些法条
We have the finest economic minds working on the bill.
谢天谢地 因税务法一直都不是你的长项
Thank God, because tax law was never your strength.
- 我真的做了很多功课 - 天呐
- I really read up about it a lot. - Oh, my God.
还记得吗? 百分之十五? 什么鬼?
Do you remember? What's 15%? What's 15%?
- 我不想再聊政治了 - 好吧
- I don't want to talk about politics anymore. - Oh, okay.
- 同意 同意 - 不谈了 你说得对
- I agree. I agree. - No, you're right.
她不能喝红酒
She can't have wine.
哦 太抱歉了
Oh, I'm so sorry.
还记得那个观光牧场吗?
Remember the dude ranch?
- 还记得那个观光牧场吗? - 哦 天呐!
- Remember the dude ranch? - Oh, my God!
- 和Vanessa! -是啊 我的天啊
- With Vanessa! - Yeah. Oh, my God...
- 我听说这有匹萨吃 - 看看谁来了
- I heard there was pizza. - Oh, look who's here!
怎么样? 你们还记得Catherine吗?
How about that? You remember Catherine.
还认得出来吗? 她减掉了所有的婴儿肥
Do you recognize her? She lost all of her baby fat.
- 还真是
- Yep.
听着 我不会把我的想法搞得人尽皆知的
Listen, I'm not gonna tell everyone what I think.
老天 我在洗手间里待不过十秒
Jeez, I wouldn't last 10 seconds in a men's room.
但私下和你们说 我认为诚实才是上策
But between us, I just think honesty is the best policy.
- 当然 - 必须的
- Sure. - Absolutely.
所以 趁着这股劲儿
So, in that spirit,
也许有人可以好心告诉我 其它的数据泄露
maybe somebody could now kindly tell me what the fuck
是他妈怎么搞的
is this other data breach.
呃 Kent?
Uh, Kent?
- Bill? - 恩?
- Bill? - Hmm?
我不管 我告诉你
I don't care. I'll tell you.
嘿 慢着慢着 真相帝
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa there, Trigger.
Mike你是政府发言人 你不可以把这讲出来
Mike, you're a spokesman. You're not supposed to say anything.
Meyer竞选利用那些死去孩子的健康档案
The Meyer campaign used the health records of dead children
来瞄准和吸引
to target and appeal to
最近失去孩子的父母们的选票
voters who were recently bereaved parents.
- 天呐 - 真是极好的 是吧
- Jesus. - It's a real doozy, huh?
看起来这个聚会被戳到静默点了
Seems like the party has hit a quiet point.
这其实没有听上去那么恶劣
It's not really as bad as it sounds.
你知道 那些孩子已经去世有一段时间了
You know, those kids have been dead for a while.
你们懂的 我可以...我可以踢翻椅子
You know, I could... I could kick over chairs
然后大叫着"到底是为啥会变成这样?"
and scream, "How in the risin' fuck did this happen?"
有什么卵用?该毁的都毁完了
What's the point? It's done.
我们得一起行动 我们可是神奇七侠
I say we move on together. The Magnificent Seven.
- 他说的真不错 - 是因为我们七个都在
- He's really good. - It's 'cause there's seven of us.
- 我是说作为一个政客 - 我知道 嗯 他...是的
- I meant as a politician. - I know. Yeah, it's... yeah.
所以 我们向前看 敬更多的破事儿
So, we move forward. To even more shit.
- 敬更多的破事儿-敬更多的破事儿
- To even more shit. - To even more shit.
你看见Tom James的"媒体见面会"没?
Did you see Tom James on "Meet the Press"?
哦 看了
Oh, yeah.
我更喜欢见他的的美体
I'd like to press his meat.
他的性感就在于他不知道自己性感 这可真是性感
He's sexy without knowing he's sexy, and that's really sexy.
现在 如果他大力宣传家庭第一提案的话 我一定会买他的账
Now, if he was selling Families First, I'd buy it for sure.
- 真的吗? - 我相信他
- Really? - I believe in him.
- 嗯哼 - 我也相信你啦
- Mm-hmm. - I believe in you, too.
- 嗯哼 好吧 - 我是说在总统的办公室里干活
- Uh-huh, right. - It's just that the office of the president
是一个非常困难的差事
is a really difficult job.
嗯哼 我来告诉你什么叫真正的困难
Mm-hmm. I'll tell you what's really difficult.
和清醒的你现在进行对话才是真正的困难
It's really difficult talking to you now that you're sober.
简直是艰难
That's tough.
好了 呃 哇哦
Okay, um, wow.
我很抱歉 但是我累了
I am sorry, but I am tired.
我是说 我也想把这个派对继续...开下去...
I mean, I would love to keep this party going for... for...
- 但是... - 谢谢款待
- But... - Thanks for having us.
- 哦 那是 应该的 - 非常感谢你
- Oh, yeah, sure. - Thank you very much.
你在吃冰淇凌?你在逗我?
You're eating ice cream? Really?
Gary 她在吃冰淇凌?
She's eating ice cream, Gary?
- 我是说... - 我就咬了一口
- I mean... - I just had a bite.
女士 有入侵者
Ma'am, intruder in the grounds.
- 现在是全面封锁! - 天哪 又来?
- This is a lockdown! - God, another one?
- 你们特么实在是逗屎我了 - 不 Gary 这跟上次是同一个人
- You've got to be shitting me. - No, Gary, it's the same one.
- 他这是在流连忘返呢 - 封锁房间!
- He's doing a victory lap. - Seal the room!
我和Jack Nicholson握着手然后我就想
I shook Jack Nicholson's hand and I thought,
"如果这只手会说话 它肯定会说'快给我洗洗吧'"
"If this hand could talk, it would say 'wash me.'"
那确实 因为那些性丑闻
Right, 'cause of all the sex stuff.
好了 大家 现在是全面封锁
Okay, everyone, this is a lockdown.
呆在那儿 别动
Stay here. Do not move.
他们就是一遍一遍地来啊来啊 直到他们干掉我们为止
They're just gonna keep coming and coming until they kill us.
- 不可能会这样 - 这就是典型的盲目模仿
- This can't be happening. - This is classic copycat.
是的 不对 这就是典型的盲目模仿
Yeah, no, it's classic copycat.
啊 就像我刚才那样
Ah, it's just like me just then.
就像 就是典型的盲目模仿
You know, it's classic copycat.
好吧 我们现在处于全面封锁
Okay, we are in lockdown.
- 现在是全面封锁 - 嘘
- This is a lockdown. - Shh.
好了 大家听着 就是现在
All right, everybody, it's that time.
现在是什么时刻? 现在就是...抽奖时间
What time is it? It's stop... raffle time.
白宫入侵者 Intruder
白宫围墙在二战后慢慢扩大范围,然
而它并不高.不时有入侵者翻墙进入.
14年9月11日及22日十天内有两次
入侵. 警方在22日入侵者Omar J.
Gonzalez的车中发现了800发子弹,
两把斧头, 一把砍刀. 他被判以18个
月监禁. 最近一次入侵发生于15年3
月2日, 入侵者于东侧行政楼门口被
拦截
抽出你的幸运大奖 耶！
Get those tickets out. Yeah!
可爱迷人的Kimberly要从这个小水泥搅拌机里随机抽取
The lovely Kimberly over here is gonna pull the winning ticket
出获奖的那张票啦 我感觉她这个抽得好
out of the cement mixer, which I thought was a nice touch.
- 让我们来看看 - 游说通常都是这么进行的吗?
- Here we go. - Is lobbying always like this?
我有种难说的不详感 它可能就是这样
I have a funny sinking feeling it might be.
如果你没有赢得大奖 不要着急
If you don't win a prize, don't worry about it.
我们会再一次点燃开奖的大加农炮
We're gonna fire up the shirt cannon one more time.
好耶 耶
Yeah. Yeah.
伙计们 这些都是免费的战利品哦
This is all free swag, guys.
玩儿得开心点吧
Have some fun.
我真希望这个入侵者直接了结了我
I wish the intruder would just kill me.
嗯 如果入侵者杀了你 Mike
Well, if the intruder kills you, Mike,
那谁来宣布你的死讯呢?
then who's gonna announce your death?
你还好吗?
You okay?
你的脸就像是难过蛋(一种表情包)
Your face looks kind of like a sad egg.
我觉得我是个骗子
I think I'm a fraud.
我一点儿也不在行
I'm not good at my job.
那个关于国王和新衣的故事
The story about the emperor and the new clothes.
我就是那个国王
I'm the emperor.
不 我是那衣服
No, I'm the clothes.
我就是那个会把我们政府搞砸的人
I'm the guy who will fuck this government.
别这样 Mike
Come on, Mike.
嘿 至少你还有一头秀发
Hey, at least you got your hair.
哦 天 我不能呼吸了 我不能呼吸了 我要窒息了
Oh, my God, I can't breathe. I  can't breathe. I can't breathe.
- 哦 亲爱的 你需要喝水 - 我得做点儿啥
- Oh, honey. You need water. - I gotta do something.
有没有人来帮助她一下?
Can somebody help her?
这些人只是来这儿保护我的 我觉得
These people are only here to protect me, I'm afraid.
- 我们会一切安好对吗? - 你会安然无恙的
- Are we gonna be okay? - You're gonna be fine.
唯一对于干掉你感兴趣的人
The only person who's interested in killing you,
就在这个房间哦 Deborah
Deborah, is here in this room.
嘿嘿 开个玩笑啦
Ahem, that was a joke.
那啥 你虽然看不见我的脸
You know, you can't see my face,
但是我确实是讲了一个笑话而已
but I'm actually making a joke.
把这个放回去
Put that back.
放回去
Put it back.
老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.